This is the story of how I finally found love...
...In London.
Yes!
Excuse me.
Siobhan! It's Roise.
Oh hi Rose.
Well... I've got myself a date!
Oh good.
Michael, can you get the baby?
I haven't actually met him yet,
I'm meeting him tonight.
But he sounds so handsome.
I think by tomorrow I could have a boyfriend.
Well Stephen's teddy is on his bed an daddy's rugby kit's
in the airing cupboard where it always is.
Not from the single's club then?
Single brain cell more like!
I want someone with some wit and sophistication.
I met him on the internet.
You know - one of those chatroom things.
So you haven't actually met him yet?
We're meeting for the first time tonight.
Well you must have seen his picture?
Well... No.
Rosie!
Well how much do you know about him?
Oh, he's sent me tonnes of emails about himself.
And..?
Well, I think he lives somewhere across town.
He says he lives in a big house.
He says his main interests are...
art...
...le cinema...
...and literature.
Oh, and apparently his mates all tell him
he looks the spitting image off...
Brad Pitt!
That's probably because his big hobby is working out in the gim.
Oh, and to top it all he says
he's really into fashion
Well - he sounds like a dream.
Yeah! Doesn't he?
After my run of luck it'll be nice
to finally meet someone...
...with some brains and some get-up-and-go.
Put it this way Siobhan -
I think I need a strong cup of tea
for my nerves.
He sounds so fantastic.
I hope I'm not going to be a let-down for him.
Oh Rosie.
And I don't know what I'm going to wear.
I haven't got a thing.
Will you calm down Rosie.
Whatever you're wearing
he's lucky to be meeting you.
Look Rose love, I've really got to go.
It's the baby's feeding time.
What time is it?
Oh - around five-thirty.
Oh God! I'd better get going too!
I'm meeting him at eight.
I bet he's not feeling this giddy.
I'll just have an orange juice please.
Could you just stick a vodka in there?
I'm not on my own you know.
I'm just waiting for a friend.
Well, he's more of a boyfriend really.
We've been exchanging emails, you know...
I think he's really fallen for me.
Hello?
Rosie! So what's he like?
How's it going tiger?
Hello? Siobhan? Is that you?
You're breaking up. I can't -
I can't hear you.
Hello?
Wrong number.
I expect he's having a bit of trouble with the trains...
... or something.
He's, um... a bit late.
I know!
If he's not here in the next thirty seconds
then he is deep in the -
Two seconds!
The next two seconds, I'm telling you!
Right! That's it! I've had enough.
If I ever see him I'm going to kill him.
I say! You've forgotten your bag.
Oh, Damn!
I can't believe he didn't even make the effort.
It'd be a shame to leave it behind.
Especially when it goes so well with your eyes.
Thanks for this.
Look, could I buy you a drink or something?
Well... It's really quiet in here tonight.
I was thinking of locking up early.
But I know a place not too far away
where they do a nice cognac.
So, do you share this place with... anyone?
No I live alone. Terribly alone.
Oh. It could do with a female touch.
It's not the only thing.
Well - can I get you that drink?
Would you like a short?
No. I'd like -
And that is the story of how I finally found love.
But I never did find out what became of my blind date.